capital.edu 2015-12-29

# Privacy | Capital University

Capital University respects your privacy as a visitor to the university's main Web site, and does not collect or disclose to others personally identifiable information about visitors.

Use of Information You Provide  
Personal information that you provide via email or through other online means will be used only for specifically stated purposes or as necessary to serve your needs, such as responding to an inquiry or request for information. This may involve redirecting your inquiry or comment to another person or department in the university to respond appropriately. Your information will not be sold or otherwise provided to third parties without your consent except as may be legally required as specified below.

#### Information We Collect and How We Use It

When you visit the Capital University family of websites we collect information regarding:

* Your Internet location (IP address)  
* Which pages you visit on our site  
* The Web page you visited before you came to our site  
* Which software you use to visit our site and its configuration

None of this information is associated with you as an individual and we cannot identify you on the basis of this information.

We do use server logs to collect information concerning your Internet connection and general information about your visit to our Web site. This information may be used in aggregate to analyze trends, to create summary statistics for the purpose of determining technical design specifications, and to identify system performance or problem areas.

This means we sometimes acquire, record and analyze portions of the data that is entered into, stored on, and/or transmitted through this site by you. This information is only released if required pursuant to law enforcement investigations, or legal proceedings, or may be used in internal investigations of Capital University policy violations. 

#### Other Web Pages

The Capital University web site provides links to other web sites within and outside the "capital.edu" domain. The university cannot be responsible for the privacy practices or content of such web sites.

Consistent with its commitment to academic freedom and free exchange of information, Capital University allows its students, student organizations, faculty and staff to produce personal web pages. These pages express the views and opinions of their authors, who are solely responsible for their contents, and do not represent official positions or policies of the University. Comments on contents of these pages should be directed to the page authors. Capital is not responsible for the content of these personal web pages or the material accessed by links from the personal web pages. However, the University reserves the right to remove any page on its servers that violates the law or university policy.

Some web pages within the "capital.edu" domain may collect personal information about visitors for specific purposes and use that information for purposes other than those stated above for the university's main web site. Each web page that collects information should have a separate privacy statement that will tell you how that information is used.

#### Contacting Us

If you have any questions about the practices of this site, please [contact the webmaster](mailto:webmaster@capital.edu?subject=Privacy%20Policy "Privacy Policy").
